

PROFILE

Software engineer with 10+ years of experience. Due to my in-depth education, as well as experience, I have solid knowledge about software concepts from object orientated development, data management to agile development processes. In addition to my ability to communicate well, I am enthusiastic about developing full-stack applications especially in JavaScript.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality

Austrian

Marital status

Married

CONTACT

- ichristiano.mail@gmail.com
- ohttps://www.netlify.com/iChristiano
- iChristiano

iChristiano

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, Research & Development

SECTOR: INDUSTRIAL AUTOMATION

2016 - current

Main focus: development & maintenance of a toolchain to improve and ensure product quality, development of web-based components for the automation industry.

Web-Engineering & Digital-Business Consulting

SECTOR: FREELANCING

2012 - current

Main focus: analysis, creation and implementation / programming (frontend/backend/data) of business models based on Internet technologies.

EDUCATION

Master of Science, Business Informatics

UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES TECHNIKUM VIENNA, AUSTRIA

2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering

UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES SALZBURG, AUSTRIA

2012 - 2014

Engineer, Electrical Engineering & Informatics

HIGHER TECHNICAL EDUCATION INSTITUTE SALZBURG, AUSTRIA

2007 - 2012

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript HTML CSS Git PMI ISTQB WebServices API Backend Frontend

FAVORITE TECHNOLOGY STACK

Node.js Express Typescript React WebdriverlO Jasmine Grunt Docker GraphQ

MongoDB PostgreSQL Redis

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

LANGUAGES

Apart of the software world, I enjoy exercising several times a week to keep my mind clear and focused. German

English